http://www.fileflash.com/privacy/

File Flash Privacy Policy
File Flash is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our many offerings. This policy may change from time to time, so please check back periodically.
Information Collection and Use
File Flash is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement.
Ad Serving Policies
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. Our third-party advertising company also separately places or recognizes a cookie file on your browser in the course of delivering advertisements to this Site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.
What personally identifiable information does File Flash collect from me?
File Flash collects very little personally identifiable information from its users. The only personally identifiable information File Flash collects is your email address. Once you register, you are no longer anonymous to File Flash. You choose a File Flash ID (user name) and are able to take full advantage of File Flash's many offerings.
What are cookies and how does File Flash use them?
As part of offering and providing customizable and personalized services, File Flash uses cookies to store and sometimes track information about you. The cookie stores your selected user name and password to save the user time, for the user will not have to log on every time they wish to access a members only function. The cookie also tracks your downloads. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. All sites on File Flash where you are prompted to log-in or that are customizable require that you accept cookies.
Sharing
We [File Flash] will share aggregated demographic information with our advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.
Our advertising companies, Fast Click, collect non-personally identifiable information about you, such as the server your computer is logged onto, your browser type (for example, Netscape or Internet Explorer), and whether you responded to the ad delivered. The non-personally identifiable information collected by Fast Click is used for the purpose of targeting ads and measuring ad effectiveness on behalf of Fast Click's advertisers and Web publishers who specifically request it.
Links
File Flash contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we [File Flash] are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.
Correction/Updating Personal Information
If a user's personally identifiable information changes (your email address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personal data provided to us. This can be done at the User Preferences page or by emailing our Webmaster.
Comments
File Flash makes use of message boards (known as Comments), available free to users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.
Communication
Registered users should not expect any unsolicited or promotional email from File Flash.
Log Files
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.
Notification of Changes
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
Home
Submit Software
Feeds
Link to Us
Privacy
©2000-2015 File Flash. All Rights Reserved.
